<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>obiserra - blog</title>
    <link>https://obiserra.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on obiserra - blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 21:28:13 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://obiserra.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dead Letter Exchange in Clojure</title>
      <link>https://obiserra.github.io/posts/rabbit-dead-letter-exchange/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2017 21:28:13 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obiserra.github.io/posts/rabbit-dead-letter-exchange/</guid>
      <description>The Problem In one of the project that I&amp;rsquo;m working on, we have several microservices that talk each other via RabbitMq messages. When the microservice A gets a message from the service B, it creates a new db record; when A gets a message from service C, it will look for an existing record and updates it. It is possible though that the message from C gets to A before the message from B, discarding the update or throwing an exception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Async Await</title>
      <link>https://obiserra.github.io/posts/async-await/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 22:00:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obiserra.github.io/posts/async-await/</guid>
      <description>The problem Our node program has to perform some operation in a precise order. In details, we want to:
 read a json file compile an Handlebar template with the result data copy all the assets in the output directory produce an html and a pdf from the compiled html  The first step is writing some asynchronous function that will return a Promise. Then we will put everything togheter using both async/await and the classic then chaining method</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Centos LAMP setup</title>
      <link>https://obiserra.github.io/posts/lamp-centos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2017 23:43:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://obiserra.github.io/posts/lamp-centos/</guid>
      <description>Start Once you are logged into the machine via ssh, you may want to check the OS you are working with, using the command
$ cat /etc/*-release  The shell output should be something like
CentOS release 6.3 (Final)  Now let’s start installing the rest of the stack
Apache To install Apache, just run
$ sudo yum install httpd  and type y when the system ask for confirm.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>